Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America: Records of Locals WAG.234
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Records of Other TWU Locals, 1937-1977.
  - Local 551 ATD: Agreements, 1970-1976 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Local 552 ATD, 1974-1975 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Local 552 ATD, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Local 552 ATD, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Local 552 ATD: Agreements, 1975, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Local 553 ATD, 1974-1983 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Local 553 ATD: Agreements, 1974 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Local 555 ATD, 1977-1979 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Local 555 ATD: Agreements (I), 1977, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Local 555 ATD: Agreements (II), 1977, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 10a)
  - Local 600 ATD, 1950-1952 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Local 700 ATD, 1952-1958 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Local 700 ATD, 1959-1960 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Local 700 ATD, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Local 700 ATD, 1962-1973 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Local 700 ATD: Agreements: 1952; 1953; 1957; 1960; 1961; 1962; 1964; 1967; 1969, 1952-1969 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    1962
  - Local 711 ATD, 1961-1963 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Local 711 ATD, 1964-1965 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Local 711 ATD, 1966-1973 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Local 711 ATD: Agreements, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Local 711 ATD: Agreements, 1967, 1969, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Local 800 ATD, 1950-1953 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Local 826 (NYC Taxi), 1956 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Local 1004, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Local 1006, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Local 1008, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Local 1013, 1948-1949 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Local 1016, 1948-1949 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Local 1020, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Local 1022, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Local 1024, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Local 1025, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Local 1026, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Local 1030, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Local 1032, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Local 1034, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Local 1038, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Local 1040, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Local 1044, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - Local 1048, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - Local 1054, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - Local 1055, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 28)
  - Local 1061, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 29)
  - Local 1063, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 30)
  - Local 1072, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 31)
  - Local 1083, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 32)
  - Local 1084, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 33)
  - Local 1085, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 34)
  - Local 1087, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 35)
  - Local 1088, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 36)
  - Local 1089, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 37)
  - Local 1136, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 38)
  - Local 1145, 1948-1949 (Box 113, Folder 39)
  - Local 1193, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 40)
  - Local 1199, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 41)
  - Local 1215, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 42)
  - Local 1220, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 43)
  - Local 1227, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 44)
  - Local 1280, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 45)
  - Local 1358, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 46)
  - Local 1372, 1948-1949 (Box 113, Folder 47)
  - Local 1373, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 48)
  - Local 1374, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 49)
  - Local 1376, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 50)
  - Local 1385, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 51)
  - Local 1387, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 52)
  - Local 1394, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 53)
  - Local 1395, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 54)
  - Local 1397, 1949-1950 (Box 113, Folder 55)
  - Local 1400 (NYC, NY), 1966-1973 (Box 113, Folder 56)
  - Local 1400, 1974-1977 (Box 113, Folder 57)
  - Local 1400: Agreements, 1967, 1968, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 58)
  - Local 1420 (Pasadena, CA), 1949 (Box 113, Folder 59)
  - Local 1425 (Glassport, PA), 1957-1959 (Box 113, Folder 60)
  - Local 1426 (Youngstown, OH), 1949-1971 (Box 113, Folder 61)
  - Local 1426: Agreements: 1960; 1961; 1966; 1972, 1960-1972 (Box 113, Folder 62)
  - Local 1427 (McKees Rocks, PA), 1955-1971 (Box 113, Folder 63)
  - Local 1427: Agreements, 1956, 1963 (Box 113, Folder 64)
  - Local 1429 (Aliquippa, PA), 1949, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 65)
  - Local 1430 (Newell, PA), 1955 (Box 113, Folder 66)
  - Local 1431, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 67)
  - Local 1432 (Aliquippa, PA), 1955-1970 (Box 113, Folder 68)
  - Local 1432: Agreements: 1955; 1956; 1958; 1960; 1963, 1955-1963, 1956, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 69)
  - Local 1438, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 70)
  - Local 1439 (Monongahela, PA), 1949, 1961-1962 (Box 113, Folder 71)
  - Local 1439: Agreements -- pre-TWU: 1941; 1942; 1945; 1946; 1949; 1950; 1951; 1952; 1953, 1941-1953 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Local 1439: Agreements: 1954; 1955; 1960; 1963 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Local 1443, 1949 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Local 1454, 1949 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Local 1459 (Hoboken, NJ), 1948-1949 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Local 1459 (Hoboken, NJ), 1957-1969 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Local 1459: Agreements, 1960 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Local 1460 (NYC, NY), 1949, 1963-1975 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Local 1460: Agreements: 1965; 1967; 1968; 1971; 1974; 1978, 1965-1978 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Local 1463 (Union City, NJ), 1949-1955 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Local 1463, 1956-1958 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Local 1463, 1959 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Local 1463, 1960-1965 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Local 1463, 1966-1971 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Local 1463, 1972-1973 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Local 1463: (United Railroad Workers of America) Day Book, Jan 1953 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Local 1463, Jul 1953-Sep 1953 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Local 1463, Oct 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Local 1463, Jan 1954-Mar 1954 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Local 1463, Apr 1954-Jun 1954 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Local 1463, Jul 1954-Sep 1954 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Local 1463, Oct 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Local 1463: Agreements, 1955-1974 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Local 1476, 1948-1950 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Local 1482, 1950 (Box 115, Folder 2a)
  - Local 1487, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Local 1515, 1950 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Local 1542, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Local 1550 (Negley, OH) [merged with 2035 in 1964], 1957-1964 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Local 1574, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 6a)
  - Local 1575, 1949-1950 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Local 1577, 1948-1950 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Local 1579 (Brookville, PA), 1957, 1964-1971 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Local 1590, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Local 1602, 1948 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Local 1608, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Local 1619 (Pittsburgh, PA), 1955 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Local 1621, 1949-1950 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Local 1622 (?), 1960 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Local 1624, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Local 1625, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - local 1627, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Local 1634 (Louisville, KY), 1955, 1964-1973 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Local 1636, 1948-1949 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Local 1642, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Local 1646, 1950 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Local 1647 (St. Louis, MO), 1949-1973 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Local 1647: Agreements, 1954-1960 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Local 1648, 1948-1949 (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - Local 1650, 1948 (Box 115, Folder 26)
  - Local 2000 (NYC, NY), 1966-1971 (Box 115, Folder 27)
  - Local 2000: Agreements, 1967, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - Local 2001 (Sunnyside, NY), 1950-1959 (Box 115, Folder 29)
  - Local 2001, 1960-1973 (Box 115, Folder 30)
  - Local 2002 (Fort Wayne, IN), 1956-1971 (Box 115, Folder 31)
  - Local 2003 (Indianapolis, IN), 1960-1973 (Box 115, Folder 32)
  - Local 2004 (Cincinnati, OH), 1960-1971 (Box 115, Folder 33)
  - Local 2005 (Columbus, OH), 1950-1959 (Box 115, Folder 34)
  - Local 2005, 1960-1971 (Box 115, Folder 35)
  - Local 2006 (Renovo, PA), 1955-1957 (Box 115, Folder 36)
  - Local 2006: Children's Letters to M.QuillFolder I, 1961-1964 (Box 115, Folder 37)
  - Local 2006: Children's Letters to M.QuillFolder II, 1963-1964 (Box 115, Folder 38)
  - Local 2006, 1965-1969 (Box 115, Folder 39)
  - Local 2007 (Altoona, PA) [merged with 2017 in 1970], 1956-1970 (Box 115, Folder 40)
  - Local 2007, 1961-1964 (Box 115, Folder 41)
  - Local 2008 (Steubenville, OH), 1950-1969 (Box 115, Folder 42)
  - Local 2009 (Pitcairn, PA), 1950-1959 (Box 115, Folder 43)
  - Local 2009, 1960-1962 (Box 115, Folder 44)
  - Local 2009, 1964-1973 (Box 115, Folder 45)
  - Local 2010 (Terre Haute, IN) [merged with 2003 in 1964], 1960-1964 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Local 2011 (Toledo, OH), 1963-1972 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Local 2012 (Philadelphia, PA), 1955-1968 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Local 2013 (Philadelphia, PA), 1955-1971 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Local 2013: Agreements, 1968 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Local 2014 (Chicago, IL), 1956-1971 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Local 2015 (Wilmington, DE), 1955-1971 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Local 2016 (Harrisburg, PA), 1955-1968 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Local 2017 (Altoona, PA), 1950-1959 (I) (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Local 2017, 1950-1959 (II) (Box 116, Folder 9a)
  - Local 2017, 1950-1959 (III) (Box 116, Folder 9b)
  - Local 2017, 1960 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Local 2017, 1961 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Local 2017, 1962 (Box 116, Folder 11a)
  - Local 2017, 1964-1966 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Local 2017, 1966-1973 (I) (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Local 2017, 1966-1973 (II) (Box 116, Folder 13a)
  - Local 2017, 1974-1975 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Local 2017, 1955-1963, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Local 2018 (Buffalo, NY), 1951-1960 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Local 2019 (Cleveland, OH), 1951-1973 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Local 2020 (Erie, PA), 1955-1971 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Local 2021 (Blairsville, PA), 1956-1974 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Local 2022 (Canton, OH), 1957-1973 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Local 2024 (Logansport, IN), 1956-1972 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Local 2025 (Baltimore, MD), 1956-1971 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Local 2026 (Wyoming, MI), 1959-1970 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Local 2027 (Cresthine, OH), 1955-1968 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Local 2028 (Williamsport, PA) [merged with 2046 in 1960], 1956-1960 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Local 2029 (Elmira, NY), 1956-1957 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Local 2030 (Wilkes-Barre, PA) [merged with 2046 in 1960] (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Local 2031 (Shire Oak, PA), 1955-1973 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Local 2032 (Youngwood, PA), 1955 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Local 2033 (Johnstown, PA), 1955-1967 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Local 2033: Agreements, 1953, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Local 2034 (Sandusky, OH) dissolved in 1964, 1956-1964 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Local 2035 (Conway, PA), 1955-1968 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Local 2035, 1971-1975 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Local 2036 (Lancaster, OH), 1955-1956 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Local 2037 (East St. Louis, MO), 1964-1972 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Local 2038 (Carnegie, PA), 1955-1960 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Local 2039 (Dennison, OH), 1955-1960 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Local 2040 (St. Louis, MO), 1956-1967 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Local 2041 (Richmond, IN), 1956-1969 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Local 2042 (?, PA), 1962-1968 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Local 2043 (Youngstown, OH), 1957, 1964-1973 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Local 2044 (Pittsburgh, PA), 1955-1971 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Local 2050 (Oil City, PA), 1956-1960 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Local 2045 (Derry, PA), 1956 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Local 2046 (Northumberland, PA), 1960 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Local 2047 (New Castle, PA), 1956-1971 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Local 2048 (Akron, OH) [merged with 2022 in 1970], 1965-1970 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Local 2049 (Ashtabula, OH), 1955-1960 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Local 2051 (Detroit, MI), 1969-1973 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Local 2052 (East Rochester, NY), 1968-1970 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Local 2053 (Elkhart, IN), 1969-1973 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Local 2054 (Boston, MA), 1970-1973 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Local 2055 (New Haven, CT), 1970-1973 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Local 3001, 1950 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Local 3002, 1950 (Box 117, Folder 33)
  - Local 3005 (Bakersfield, CA), 1956-1970 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - Local 3005: Agreements: 1955; 1956; 1960; 1961; 1962; 1963, 1955-1963 (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - Local 3006 (Belen, NM), 1955-1970 (Box 117, Folder 36)
  - Local 3006: Agreements: 1956; 1958; 1962; 1964; 1972, 1956-1972 (Box 117, Folder 37)
  - Local 4001 (Norfolk, VA), 1959 (Box 117, Folder 38)
  - Local 4002 (Altoona, PA) [merged with 2007 in 1960] (Box 117, Folder 39)
- Series III: Records of TWU Local 100 (New York City), Addendum (Unprocessed Material)
  - Token Booths/Fare, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Implementation Outreach, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Implementation, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Appeals, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Vote Counts, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Rulings (from Nick), 2004 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Sonny - I'm Sorry, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Mscl, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Local 3 Bill, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - 2003 Womens Retreat (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - TWU Local 100 Memo, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - CED Plan, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Time Management, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Turn of the Wheel, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Pol Act, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Staff Meetings, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Staff Memos, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - NU/rt, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - CINTAS, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Staff Disputes, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Ordinary Death Benefits, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Level 2 and Level 3 Grievance, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Leadership Training Notes, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Leadership Training, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Training, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - Workshops, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - Officers Training, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - Training Needs Survey, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - PBL Political Contributions, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 29)
  - 70th Anniversary Year, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 30)
  - SOS Queens, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - ABB Button, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - Florida Retirees Journal, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - Domestic Violence, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - Hurricane Relief, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - Election, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 36)
  - TWU Cope, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 37)
  - Clyde Hines Hip Hop Museum, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 38)
  - Bus Cleaners, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 39)
  - MTA Threats, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 40)
  - Attendance Reports, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 41)
  - HIP Conversion, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 42)
  - Bus, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 43)
  - Station Reporter et al, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 44)
  - Transportation Summit Emergency, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 45)
  - Bus Assault, etc., 2004 (Box 118, Folder 46)
  - Political Activist List/Labels, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 47)
  - Sick Control, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 48)
  - Subsidy Accountability/JWJ, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 49)
  - Train Security/Training, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 50)
  - Samuelsen/Track, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 51)
  - Worker Family Party, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 52)
  - Telecom Titles, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 53)
  - Queens College Local 100, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 54)
  - Response to Sonny, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 55)
  - PBL Staff, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 56)
  - PolAct Follow Up, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 57)
  - Bus Death, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 58)
  - Ordinary Death Benefit Calculation, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 59)
  - QPBL, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 60)
  - OA Death Pension Benefit Calculation, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 61)
  - PBL-RT, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 62)
  - ODB, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 63)
  - Packet, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 64)
  - Bus Captains, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 65)
  - Lobby Day, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 66)
  - Packet, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 67)
  - NY Labor Day, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 68)
  - Lobby Day 2003 (Box 118, Folder 69)
  - Local 100 Lobby Day 2004 (Box 118, Folder 70)
  - 2/18 Stewards (Box 118, Folder 71)
  - Family Day, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 72)
  - TA Surface Maintenance Contract Demands, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 73)
  - Bus Assaults, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 74)
  - Extra Packet Stuff, 2000s (Box 118, Folder 75)
  - Strike Photo Exhibit Essay Contest Contestant Manuscripts Binder #1, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Strike Photo Exhibit Essay Contest Contestant Manuscripts Binder #3, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Strike Photo Exhibit Essay Coontest Contestant Manuscripts Binder #6, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Strike Photo Exhibit Essay Contest Contestant Manuscripts Binder #2, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Strike Photo Exhibit Essay Contest Contestant Manuscripts Binder #5, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - TWU Publications, Memoranda, Schedules, 2000s (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Mail Assignments and Contact List, 2000s (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - TWU Local 100 Activity, Agenda, Publicity, 2000s (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Strike Letters 2006 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - TA Surface, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Workers' Compensation Navigator Program: Union Member Workbook, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - PBL Comp, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - COMP, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Workers Comp/Richard Frank, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Queens PBL Negotiations, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Queens Meeting, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Jennings, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - PBL NU, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - PBL, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Lit, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - PBL Memos, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Queens Division Officers Meetings, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Queens PBL 1/19/03, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - QSC Survey, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Jamaica, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - News Release, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Greenwich, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Westchester Classes, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Comp Tech, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Vendors, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Membership Lists, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - School Bus HealthCare, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Implementation Campaign, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Legal Services, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - PBL Staff Meetings, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Queens Surface, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Wanda Vega Queens Surface, 2002-2003 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Queens PBL HBT, 2002-2003 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Triboro, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - PBGC, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Liberty Lines/Westchester/Mooney, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Liberty EAP/UAP, 2001-2004 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - NY Bus/Liberty, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - NY Bus/Denicolo, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - First Transit, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - American Transit Health, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - ENZO, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - Bill Mooney, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 39)
  - Re-Run Elections, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 40)
  - Local 100 Information Packet, Contact List, & Memoranda, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 41)
  - Political Action Team Lobby Day Debriefing & Lobby Day Info, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 42)
  - Local 100 Contract Ratification Campaign, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 43)
  - Scheinman Temp Bill, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 44)
  - Battle Plans, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 45)
  - Ballot Reminder Fax, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 46)
  - Battle Reports, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 47)
  - Ratification, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 48)
  - Bus/OA/TA, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 49)
  - VOTE NO, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 50)
  - Scheinman, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 51)
  - Pension and Welfare Aspects of Private Lines consolidation, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 52)
  - SOS Queens, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 53)
  - 4/28 Meeting, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 54)
  - SOS Queens, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 55)
  - MTA Takeover, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 56)
  - Labor Statements/PBL, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 57)
  - Queens Private Lines Contract Survey Publicity, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 58)
  - Publicity, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 59)
  - Queens Surface Balance Sheets, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 60)
  - 4/29 Membership Meeting, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 61)
  - Takeover Background Papers, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 62)
  - 6/22 Emergency Lobby Day, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 63)
  - 5-21 Membership Meeting, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 64)
  - Queens Negotiations, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 65)
  - MTA 4/24, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 66)
  - 4/22 ATU/TWU Meeting on Breakaway, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 67)
  - 5/19 MTA Meeting, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 68)
  - PBL Survey - Urban Agenda, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 69)
  - Work Plan, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 70)
  - Bronx Event, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 71)
  - RBA, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 72)
  - The Queens Economy Rides the Bus, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 73)
  - Venezuela, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 74)
  - SSSA, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 75)
  - Bus Consolidation, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 76)
  - Family Day 2003 (Box 120, Folder 77)
  - Unsung Heroes, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 78)
  - Uniforms, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 79)
  - Sandhogs, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 80)
  - Abestos, 2000s (Box 120, Folder 81)
  - Million Worker March, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 82)
  - Strike, 2002 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Breakaway, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - IWFR, 2000s (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - PV'T Line Strike (Ans, Tri, Jam), 2000s (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Special Bulletins, Agenda, and News Clippings, 2000s (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - John E. Lawe Tribute/Fundraiser duplicate, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 024)
  - Unprocessed 2" broadcast videotapes (21). Includes 1961 TWU Convention, Dub of Phil Muray Memorial Show, 1963 Railroad Crisis, 1961-1968 (Box 122, Box 123, Box 124, Box 125, Box 126, Box 127, Box 128, Box 129, Box 130, Box 131, Box 132, Box 133, Box 134, Box 135, Box 136, Box 137, Box 138, Box 139, Box 140, Box 141, Box 142)